TRUONG KHUONG XUAN

Career Objective

1-3 year next: follow high pressure environment, work with long time, learn skills and experience, Become team leader, manage project or more.

5 year next: My dream is my owner company. I will try my best to follow my dream and my career, although current time is so difficult to build my dream.

Work Experience

Having experience in Microsoft Technologies like .NET frame work (2.0, 3.0, 3.5, 4.0), ASP.NET(VB, C++, C#), ADO.NET, SQL Server, MS Access.

Having experience and proficient in **PHP**, **MySQL**, and associated technologies like XML, XSL transformations, JavaScript, VB Script, JQuery & Ajax, ect.

Having experience and proficient in Web Development with CSS 2-3, **Jquery**, **Ajax**, Cross Browser, WebStyleGuide, **Web responsive**, **Web mobile** ...

My work experience involves right from Desktop development to experience rich Internet Applications.

Academic Credentials

Colleges Bachelor B.English	Colleges Bachelor of IT in *********Colleges Center supports the development of	60% 60%	2005-2008 2007
	information technology applications in foreign language		
Bachelor of IT	Bachelor of IT in <i>University of Science</i> ********* City	70%	2008-2010

IT Skill set

Languages : .NET, PHP, Java, HTML, JQuery, Script
Technical Tools : Asp.net, Ado.net, MVC, 3tier, 3 layer
Database : SOL Server******** MySOL. Access

Operating system : Windows 2000 / 2003, Windows XP, Windows Seven, linux

Software Packages : MS-Office ...

Designing Tools : HTML, Java Script, VB Script, Visio, PowerDesigner,

MsProject, Rational ROSE, Eclips, NetBean...

Project Work

2010 – Now: Creating Mobile Responsive(or Full Screen) project as: <u>HTTP://LEMEDIA.IN</u>, <u>HTTP://MOODYCRAB.COM.AU/home</u>, <u>HTTP://GRAVITYPLUS.ASIA/home</u>, http://banhyeu.com/(create and develop cms, backend, frontend but it's coming soon at now).

BÁNH YÊU (2014)

• Url : http://carrerakitchens.com.au/

• Team size : 3

Technologies : Bootstrap 3 – responsive, jqwidget, css3, jquery, php
 Task : Create templates, develop (backend, frontend).

CARRENA KITCHEN – Freelancer (2013)

• Url : http://banhyeu.com/

• Team size : 2

• Technologies : Bootstrap 3 – responsive, jqwidget, css3, jquery, php

• Task : Create templates, develop (backend, frontend).

THIÊN THẦN TRUYỆN - MECORP(2013)

Url : http://3t.mobo.vn/

• Team size : 5

• Technologies : Bootstrap 3 – responsive, jqwidget, css3, jquery, php, extjs

• Task : Create templates (home site, teaser, intro, subweb ...), develop (backend, frontend, event, api, forum ...).

DEAL GIA DUNG – Freelancer(2012)

Url : http://dealgiadung.com/

• Team size : 3

Technologies : Grid 960, jqwidget, css3, jquery, php

Task : Create templates, develop (backend, frontend, order, payment).

Read To My Child – Freelancer(2013)

Url : http://readtomychild.com.au/

• Team size : 3

• Technologies : Grid 960, jawidget, css3, jauery, php

Task : Create templates, develop (backend, frontend, order, payment).

MIND WORK – Freelancer(2012)

• Url : http://mindworktraining.com/

• Team size : 2

• Technologies : Grid 960, jqwidget, css3, jquery, php

• Task : Create templates, develop (backend, frontend, order, payment).

TÂY DU KÝ(Hắc Ám Tây Du) - MECORP(2013)

• Url : http://hacam.vn/

• Team size : 4

Technologies : Sencha touch, jqwidget, extjs, css3, jquery, php, mobile detect

• Task : Create templates (home site, teaser, intro, subweb ...), develop (backend, frontend, event, api, forum ...).

MÃNH THÚ – MECORP (2013)

Url : http://mt.mobo.vn/

Team size : 4

Technologies : jqwidget, extjs, css3, jquery, php, mobile detect

• Task : Create templates (home site, teaser, intro, subweb ...), develop (backend, frontend, event, api, forum ...).

THỐNG LĨNH, THÀNH CÁT, LONG TINH, KỲ TIÊN , CƠN LỐC SÂN CỔ , ĐẠI CHIẾN RAU CỦ-MECORP(2013)

Url : http://thonglinh.com/, <a href="http://thong

• Team size : 3-5

• Technologies : css2, jquery, php, mobile detect, useragent detect

• Task : Create templates (web, swap, wap, teaser, intro, subweb ...), develop (backend, frontend, event, api, forum ...).

CỬU ÂM CHÂN KINH – GOSU(2013)

Url : http://cuuam.gosu.vn/

• Team size : 5

• Technologies : css3, jquery, php

Task : Create templates (web , teaser, intro, subweb ...), develop (backend, frontend, event, api ...*******/2013 to Now develop Game Service at Mecorp as Long tinh, Kỳ Tiên, Tây du ký, Thành cát, Thống lĩnh, mãnh thú, thiên thần truyện, Cơn lốc sân cỏ, Mãnh thú, Đại chiến rau củ work as website developer, "out game" event, develop API...

06/2012 to 03/2013 join and develop Game Service Gosu as programmer and lead. Deploy events for "out game", chanelling for developing game process of company. Develop necessary API, tool, plug-in for developing game process..

Ngao Kiếm: develop website: login-play, events, and tester.

Cơn Lốc Sân Cổ: develop website, include functions: giftcode, app facebook Voting Euro 2012

<u>Tiên Kiếm</u>: develop website: tester, giftcode, <u>chanelling with Zing Me</u>

<u>Bá Đao</u>: develop website with functions Alpha test, login-play, giftcode, signal event, gamble, teaser, chanelling với Zing Me

<u>Tiên Lac Phàm Trần</u>: develop website with functions teaser, home, login-play, giftcode, event, chanelling with NCT

Freelancer

From 2012 to Nows: Join outsource project as Website <u>Dealgiadung.com</u>, <u>readtomychild.com.au</u>, <u>pushclimbing.com</u>, <u>http://mindworktraining.com</u>, <u>http://carrerakitchens.com.au/, http://lemedia.in, http://pxq.vn, http://http://gravityplus.asia</u>

Other

Biz Admin Tool Website - PHP (01/2012 to 04/2012)

Design and develop "Admin website" for internal team, include functions: Game Investor/ developer, Game publisher, Payment gateway, online/offline/web/social/mobile Games at Southeast Asia Market...

Neowiz Website - PHP (01/2012 to 02/2012)

Design and develop introducing website for Korean Game at Southeast Asia Market (as well as Blue Moon), website for company.

TV Show in JukeOn Website - PHP (11/2011 to 12/2011)

Design and develop website: introduce, watching TV show for KtoU, JukeOn TV, Kmusic. Voting songs, artist...

SMS gateway - PHP (09/2011 to 10/2011)

Design and develop system manage SMS (SMS Service) for 8x88.

JukeOn Shopping Website - PHP (06/2011 to 9/2011)

Design and develop Shopping Online website, include online payment with Ngan Luong, Bao Kim Gatway.

JukeOn Website - PHP (03/2011 to 9/2011)

Design and develop Admin website: manage licence of Korean music, contract Korean Music with Music Content Provider at Vietnam, Report monthly revenue...

Work experience

- Professional training in Colleges Bachelor of IT in ********Colleges and University of Science ******** City
- Developer in Neowiz Internet Vietnam One Member Co., Ltd (36 TrươngQuyền, P.6, Quận 3, TP.HồChí

Minh)

Duration : From 11-2010 to 03-2012

Work : Development for "JukeOnwebsite."

Development for "Shopping Online website."

Development for "SMS Gateway".

Development for "TV Show website".

Salary : ****** vnd

Reasons to quit : Looking for new work environment.

Programmer at CÔNG TY CPDV PHÂN MÊM MĂT TRÒI (10 Phổ Quang, Phường 2, Quận Tân Bình,

TP.HCM)

Duration : 03-2011 to 04-2012

Position : Vice-Team Leader – Software Technology

Work : develop website home, teaser, event ("out game" as giftcode, auction, signature) for GOSU Game (Ngạo Kiếm II, Cơn Lốc Sân Cỏ, Vạn Vương Chi Vương, Bá Đao, Tiên Kiếm, Tiên Lac Phàm Trần).

Create chanelling (connect and Payment) game with partner Zing Me, NCT(nhạc của tui), VTC.

Create app facebook for games (app horoscope, app Football Voting).

Build API, Tools, Plug-in for developing Game process.

Salary : ******* vnd(16 month/year)
Reasons to quit : Looking for new work environment.

Programmer at CÔNG TY Giải Trí Di Động (ME) (141 *********, Phường 7, Quận 3, Tp. HCM)

Duration : 04-2013 to Nows Position : **Programmer**

Work : develop websites home, teaser, events (out game: giftcode, auction, signature) for ME (Game: Tây du ký, thành cát, Long Tinh, Kỳ Tiên, iWin,Thống lĩnh, Mãnh thú, Thiên thần truyện, Bóng đá).

Build APIs, Tools, Plug-in for developing Game process.

Salary :

Personal Dossier

Full Name : Truong Khuong Xuan

Address : 181/19 ********, Ward 10, Distr T******* - HCM City

Skype : khuongxuantruong